你认为怎么样？
So what do you think?
乔伊的房间（法语）
Casa de Joey.
我自己布置的 少来了
-I decorated it myself. -Get out!
乔伊，这个是…
Wow,Joey,this is....
艺术 就是艺术
-Art. -Art it is.
瞧，这是一张咖啡桌呢
Check this out! Is it a coffee table?
还是一只豹？都无所谓
Is it a panther? There's no need to decide.
好漂亮的枕头
Hey,nice pillow.
这是真的布偶皮吗？
So tell me,is this genuine Muppet skin?
好极了，桌上型水东西
Hey,excellent water,table thing.
谢了，我很喜欢这个东西 但你知道吗？
Thanks. I love this. But you know what?
它会让我想尿尿
It makes me want to pee.
对呀，我也是 对呀，我想挑战就在那儿
Yeah,me too. I think that's the challenge.
为什么钱德没来？
How come Chandler didn't come?
因为他有一件事…
It's because he had a thing with the...
…他有事
...with the thing.
我懂了
Right. I got it.
带我们去参观你房间（法语）其他的部分吧
So why don't you show us the rest of your casa?
最棒的部分，来…
The best part! Come on.
好帅的马桶
Nice toilet.
不…后面那个
No,no,no. Behind it.
你这里装了电话？ 没错
-You have a phone in here? -That's right.
我这里装了…
I have a phone.
…电话
In here.
乔伊，答应我一件事
Joey,promise me something.
别用那个电话打给我
Never call me from that phone.
六人行 第2季 第17集 艾迪搬入
The One Where Eddie Moves ln
来了
Okay,here we go.
抱歉，苹果派卖完了 最后一片刚没有了
Sorry,they were all out of apple pie. Someone just got the last piece.
天啊…你们绝对不会相信的
Oh,my God! You won't believe this!
我刚刚被发现了
I have just been discovered.
等一等，我四年前 就宣布你为法国领地了
Wait a minute. I claimed you in the name of France four years ago.
总而言之
Anyway.
答应我，你们不会发狂 直到我说完为止，好吗？
Don't freak out and say how great this is until I'm done.
我刚刚认识了一个 小唱片公司的制作人…
I just met this producer of this teeny record company...
…她说我的声音很清新 很特别…
...who said that I have a very fresh,offbeat sound...
…她要帮我录制 “臭臭猫”的试听带
...and she wants to do a demo of "Smelly Cat."
我说过不要太兴奋的
Okay,I told you not to do that yet.
她还说要帮我做音乐电视呢
And she wants to do a video.
我还没说完
I'm not done yet,okay?
天哪
God!
如果结果不错的话 他们或许还会帮我做一个专辑
If that goes well,they may even want to make an album.
我说完了
I'm done now.
罗斯，如果你关心我的话 就把馅饼从他帽子里拿出来
If you care about me,get the pie out of the man's hood.
拿什么？ 帽子里有馅饼…快去
-Get the what? -There's a pie in the hood. Go!
你干什么？
What are you doing?
对不起，我的馅饼… 在…在你帽子里
I'm sorry. My pie was in your hood.
现在我得去那个家伙的裤子上 拿我的咖啡…
I have to get the coffee out of that guy's pants...
…我七点以前会回医院去
...and I'll be back in the hospital by 7.
该死，罗斯，你快给我滚出来
Damn it,Ross! Get your butt out of the bathroom!
别激动，我在吹头发
Calm down. I'm blow-drying.
吹什么头发呀？你没有头发啦
Blow-drying what? You have no hair.
怎么了？
What's going on?
你男朋友 在里面关了一个多小时
Your boyfriend has been in there for an hour!
真不敢相信 这就像我们又住在一起
It's like I'm living with him again.
我睡觉时他在，醒来时他在 想洗澡的时候他也在
He's here when I go to sleep and wake up and when I want to shower.
我好像回到十六岁了
I feel like I'm 16 again.
你不是十六岁 而且你们现在都是大人了
Well,you're not 16. You're both adults now.
出来呀，蠢货
Get out,you doofus!
你知道啊 他是橡胶，你是胶水
Or,you know,he's rubber and you're glue.
该你了
All yours.
希望你清了排水孔的头发
I hope you cleaned your hair out of the drain.
住口
Shut up!
停止
Cut it out!
我从来没有这样想要过你
I've never wanted you more.
你好
Hello?
-路易吗？霍华德在哪？-他回家了
-Louie? Where's Howard?N-He went home
他说他换班后可能上来看看的
He said he might stop by after a shift.
他说他告诉过你他不太舒服
He said he tell you he don't feel so good.
你什么时候换班
Hey what time do you get off?
我也不太舒服
I'm not feeling too good either
怎么样，孩子们 我该打电话给他吗？
So what do you say,boys? Should I call him?
他们说：
You know what they say:
问你拖鞋一个问题…
Ask your slippers a question...
…你疯了
...you're going crazy.
畸形的艺术品
Freaking art!
乔伊，对不起 我今天没有过去
I'm sorry I didn't make it over there today.
没关系
That's okay.
你…你有事嘛
You had a thing.
对，听说你那里很棒
I hear the place looks great.
别提了，我开心死了
Forget about it. I'm having a ball!
你那儿怎么样了？
How's the apartment?
很…很棒啊 一个空间…
It's terrific. I mean,it's a regular space-...
…的大聚合
...-fest!
那太棒了
Well,great.
是呀，我只是…
Yeah,I just...
…打个电话跟你聊一聊而已
...wanted to call and say hey.
好啊
Well,okay.
那是烤箱定时器吗？
Was that the oven timer?
没有错，朋友
That's right,my friend.
应该看…
It's time for...
…“海滩游侠”了
...Baywatch!
你相信 他们让斯戴芬妮得皮肤癌吗？
Can you believe they gave Stephanie skin cancer?
我还是不敢相信 他们升她为副队长
I can't believe they made her lieutenant!
你那么说是因为 你最喜欢杰丝敏碧利斯了
You're saying that because you love Yasmine Bleeth.
怎么可能会有人 不爱杰丝敏碧利斯呢？
How could anyone not love Yasmine Bleeth?
她们在跑了
Hey,they're running.
瞧，这个节目棒就棒在这里
See,this is the brilliance of the show.
我说她们应该不停地跑
I say always keep them running.
一直跑
All the time running!
跑
Run!
跑啊，杰丝敏，像风一样的跑
Run,Yasmine! Run like the wind!
我以为你想自己一个人住
But you wanted to live by yourself.
没错，我以为会很棒
I did. I thought it'd be great.
我以为我会有时间自己思考
I figured I'd have time alone with my thoughts.
但我发觉我的思想 没有你们想的那么多
But it turns out I don't have as many thoughts as you think.
乔伊，你跟钱德说 你想搬回去好了
Why don't you talk to Chandler about moving back?
你认为他会答应吗？
You really think he'd take me?
我们昨晚聊得很开心…
We had a good talk last night...
…可是我搬走时把他伤透了
...but when I moved out,I hurt him bad.
我保证，他绝对想你搬回去的
He would definitely want you back.
我告诉你 他绝对不可能搬回来的
I'm telling you,there's no way he's moving back.
可是我们从没像昨天晚上 聊得那么开心过
But we had one of the greatest talks we ever had last night.
那就像是…
I mean,it was
我们刚刚住在一起时一样
It was like when we first started living together.
钱德 我知道你现在听不进去…
I know you don't want to hear this right now...
…但我们看过他在新家的样子 他很快乐
... but we've seen him in his new place. And he's happy.
他都装潢好了
He's decorated.
听着，钱德 他向前走了，你也要这样
Chandler,he has moved on,okay? You have to,too.
你必须接受 你们只是朋友这个事实
You'll have to accept the fact that you're just friends now.
你们不再是…
You're not...
…室友了
... roommates anymore.
菲比，可以试了吗？
Okay,Phoebe. You ready to try one?
臭臭猫，臭臭猫
Smelly cat,smelly cat
他们喂你什么？
What are they feeding you?
非常臭的臭臭猫
Smelly,smelly,smelly Really bad smelling smelly cat
我的天啊
Whoa! Oh,my God!
是谁在唱？
I mean,like,who was that?
你的伴唱团，在你后面
They're your backup singers. Behind you,hon.
我还以为她们只是在看
I thought they were just watching me.
就像水族馆那样
Like at an aquarium,you know?
-她们很棒，你们很棒！-好的
-They' re so good. You' re so good! -All right.
好的，现在每个人都认识了，我们再试一次
Okay, now that everyone knows everyone, let's try it again.
从头开始
From the top.
臭臭猫，臭臭猫
Smelly cat,smelly cat
他们喂你什么？
What are they feeding you?
对不起
Okay,sorry.
我没感觉到…
I'm just not getting...
…大家都懂…
...that everyone gets...
…这只猫到底有多臭
... how smelly this cat actually is.
也许我们应该谈一谈…
Maybe if we could talk about this...
…因为我必须要感觉到 你们真的…很关心那只猫
... because I need to feel that you really care about the cat.
我们可以谈的
We can talk.
只是录音间是算时间的 一分钟一百块耶
It's just that this costs $100 a minute to be in here.
好，那只猫很臭 但你们非常爱它，开始
So the cat stinks,but you love it. Let's go.
不，它绝对不可能是一只迅猛龙的
No,there is no way he was a velociraptor.
不，东尼，你看它的头盖脊骨
Look at the cranial ridge,okay?
帝诺要是一只迅猛龙 它早吃了摩登原始人（动画）了
If Dino was a velociraptor,he'd have eaten the Flintstones.
你在睡觉？
Were you taking a nap?
本来是
I was.
等等，东尼，等一下，好吗？ 我有电话进来
Tony,can you hold on? That's the other line.
对，她在 我叫她回电话，好吗？
Yeah,she's here,but can she call you back?
好，谢了
Okay,thanks.
打给乔安娜
Call Joanna.
她留了号码？
Did she leave a number?
你看到我写下来了吗？
Did you see me write one down?
我没有她的电话，呆瓜
I don't have her number,butt-munch.
那她会再打来的 你不要耍孩子脾气了
She'll call back. Don't be such a baby.
我才没有，你自己才是
You're the baby.
听着，你别烦我，好不好？ 你不要碍眼，好不好？
-Get off my back. -Get out of my face.
慢着，等一下，东尼
Wait,hold on,Tony. Hold on.
对，不，她在，等一下
Yeah,she's right here. Hold on.
东尼，我再打给你，好吗？
Tony,can I call you back?
那是我妹妹的男朋友
That's my sister's boyfriend.
电话给我
Give me that.
甜心，听着，趁我还记得 我的避孕器是否留在你那儿？
Sweetie,before I forget,did l leave my diaphragm at your place?
妈
Hi,Mom.
皇宫生活过得怎么样了？
So how's the palace?
真有趣，既然你提起这个 我在想…
It's funny you should mention that because I was thinking....
这些箱子怎么回事？
What's with the boxes?
事实上，我有个消息
Actually,I have some news.
那个乔伊会回来拿他的 麋鹿帽吗？还是我把它扔了？
Is that Joey guy gonna pick up his moose hat or should I toss it?
这个…你何不自己问他呢？ 乔伊，这是我的新室友艾迪
Why don't you ask him yourself? This is my new roommate,Eddie.
幸会
Nice to meet you.
彼此 你好吗？
-Likewise. -How you doing?
那我带走了
I'll take that.
我就是回来拿这个的
It's what I came for.
这倒新鲜 你们是哪儿认识的？
This is new. Where'd you two meet?
我们在超市的民族食品区
At the supermarket in the ethnic food section.
我帮他挑西班牙香肠
I helped him pick out a chorizo.
我们开始聊，他说要找地方住 而我又刚好有一个空房
We got to talking. He needed a place,and I had a spare room.
那儿成了空房了？
Now it's a spare room?
是啊，那房间没有人用…
Well,yeah. In that it's not being used...
…而我就把它空出来
...and I have it to spare.
我拿到我要的了
Well,I got what I came for.
改天见了
I'll see you.
乔伊
Hey,Joe.
你什么时候开始抹摩丝的？
When'd you start using moose in your hair?
他是不是很棒？
Is this guy great,or what?
是呀，他很棒
Yeah,he is.
真不敢相信他有新室友了 这家伙是谁啊？
I can't believe he has a new roommate. Who is he?
好像叫艾迪，他们刚认识
Eddie. He just met him.
不会长久的，他只是个室友替代品
It'll never last. He's just a rebound roommate.
看这个…
Check it out! Check it out!
是“臭臭猫”的音乐电视
It's "Smelly Cat," the video!
我自己都还没看呢 如果你们不喜欢的话呢…
Now,I haven't seen it yet,so if you don't like it...
…那又怎么样？ 你们又没有音乐电视
...so what? None of you ever made a video.
滚出去，猫，你臭死了
Get out of here,cat! You stink!
冒烟耶
Smoking!
看看我
Look at me!
臭臭猫，臭臭猫
Smelly cat,smelly cat
他们喂你什么？
What are they feeding you?
臭臭猫，臭臭猫
Smelly cat,smelly cat
那不是你的错
It's not your fault
臭臭…，非常臭的臭臭猫
Smelly,smelly,smelly Really bad smelling smelly cat
那不是你的错
It's not your fault
臭臭猫…
Smelly cat,smelly cat
我的天啊 我知道
-Oh,my God! -I know.
我的声音好美喔
I sound amazing!
他们不带你去看兽医
They won't take you to the vet
你显然不是他们的最爱
You're obviously not their favorite pet
臭臭猫，臭臭猫
Smelly cat,smelly cat
那不是你的错
It's not your fault
我从没听过自己唱的歌
I've never heard myself sing before.
除了在我自己的头里面
I mean,except in my own head.
这太酷了 我可以听到你们听到的了
This is so cool! Now I can hear what you hear!
蛮不同的吧？
Pretty different,huh?
不好意思，我实在太才华洋溢
I am sorry,but I'm incredibly talented!
臭臭猫，臭臭猫
Smelly cat,smelly cat
那不是你的错
It's not your fault
乔伊，近来如何？
What's going on,man?
艾迪
Eddie.
早安
Morning.
我只是过来拿我的信
I just came by to pick up my mail.
信在哪儿？ 在那边那张桌上
-Where's the mail? -Over there on the table.
你不再把信放在这张桌上了？
You don't keep it on this table anymore?
不了，艾迪喜欢把信放在那边
Eddie likes it over there.
好了，请用吧，朋友 这是艾迪风格的鸡蛋
All right,here you go,my friend. Eggs a la Eddie.
太棒了
That's great.
干嘛？
What?
我只是以为你喜欢…
I thought you liked your eggs...
…面包挖一个洞，中间放蛋呢，我的风格
...with the bread with the hole in the middle,a la me!
我是喜欢呀，但艾迪是这样煎的，还真的是蛮好吃的
I do,but Eddie makes them this way. They're pretty darn good.
-想尝尝吗？-不了，谢谢
-Wanna try some?-No, thanks.
好了，两位…
Well,you guys...
…我要出去了
... I'm out of here.
再见，兄弟们
See you,pals.
再见
See you.
你们处得怎么样？ 再快乐也不过了
-How are you two getting along? -I couldn't be happier.
很好
Great.
我替你高兴
I'm happy for you.
好吧，够了
All right,that's it!
那个人就这样进来 新蛋先生…
He just comes in here,Mr. Johnny New Eggs...
…变了放信的地方，还有 “再见，兄弟们”
...with his moving the mail and his "See you,pals."
现在果汁也没有了
And now there's no juice!
需要果汁的人没果汁喝 我需要果汁
There's no juice for the people who need the juice. I need the juice!
那边还有一盒果汁啊
There's another carton there.
这不再是关于果汁的事了，好吗？
This isn't about juice anymore,all right,man?
好呀
All right.
那么是关于什么呢？
So what's it about?
蛋
Eggs!
你比较喜欢谁的蛋？ 他的还是我的？
Whose eggs do you like better,his or mine?
我两个一样喜欢 少来了
-Well,I like both eggs equally. -Oh,come on!
没人一样喜欢两种不同的蛋 我知道你比较喜欢哪一种
Nobody likes two eggs equally. I wanna know which one you like better.
那有什么差别呢？ 你的蛋已经不在这个地方了
What's the difference? Your eggs aren't here anymore.
你已经带着你的蛋走了
You took your eggs and you left!
你真的期望 我再也找不到一个新的蛋吗？
Did you expect me to never find new eggs?
也许这不是关于蛋的问题
Maybe this isn't about the eggs.
也许是生蛋的鸡的问题
Maybe this is about the chicken that laid them.
什么鸡？哪有鸡？
What chicken?There's no chicken.
我没法跟你沟通
I can't talk to you!
我要看“今夜娱乐”
I wanna watch Entertainment Tonight.
真不幸 我们要看“塞伦盖蒂野生国家公园的掠食者”
Tough. We're watching Predators of the Serengeti.
不要吵了，好不好？
Would you guys stop!
这是我的电视
It's my TV!
你…住手 你咬我呀
-Quit it! -Bite me!
莫妮卡她一直在转台呀
Monica keeps changing the channel.
棒极了 你去跟妈咪告状啊
That's great. Why don't you tell Mommy on me?
现在我变成妈咪了
Now I'm Mommy in this little play?
好，听着，我拒绝卷入…
Look,I refuse to get sucked into...
…这一类畸型的盖勒家庭纠纷
...this weird little Geller dimension thing,okay?
我现在要去洗个 香喷喷热腾腾的泡泡浴…
So I'm gonna go take a nice long hot bubble bath...
…因为妈咪快要被你们逼疯了
...because you kids are driving me crazy!
这件事我们怎么解决？
What do we do about this?
我们可以 把“今夜娱乐”录下来
We could tape Entertainment Tonight.
不是那个
Not that!
我是说这个，我们！
This! Us!
天啊，罗斯，你…你只是你…
Oh,my God,Ross,it's.... You're just....
从你到这儿开始 我都快要被你逼疯了…
Since you've been here,you're driving me....
莫妮卡，你又开始超声波了
Mon,you've gone ultrasonic again,all right?
我受不了…
I just can't stand you being here...
…你老是在这里！
...all the time!
为什么？ 你为什么受不了呢？
Why? Why can't you stand me being here?
我们只是在闹着玩而已
We're just having fun.
玩？这叫好玩吗？
Fun? You think this is fun?
我以为我们只是在闹 就像我们小时候一样
I thought we were fooling around,like when we were kids.
罗斯，小时候我恨你耶
I hated you when we were kids!
小时候你恨我？
You hated me when we were kids?
对，我恨你
I hated you.
我是说，我就像“你是我哥 所以我必须爱你”那样爱你…
I loved you in a you're-my-brother- so-l-have-to way...
…但基本上…我恨死你了
... but basically,I hated your guts.
你为什么要恨我？
Why did you hate me?
因为你对我太残忍了…
Because you were mean to me...
而且…你…你嘲弄我 你总是…你总是得逞
...and you teased me and you always got your way.
你觉得那不好玩？
That wasn't fun for you?
真不敢相信你恨我
I can't believe you hated me.
现在我爱你
But now I love you.
不只是因为我必须这样
And not just because I have to.
真的？
Really?
只是你现在必须停止惹怒我
You're just gonna have to stop pissing me off.
我可以办得到
I can do that.
那我就用不着杀你了
Then I won't have to kill you.
你要看“今天娱乐”？
So you wanna watch Entertainment Tonight?.
谢了
Thanks.
知道吗？
You know what?
如果你真的想看那个节目 我还是可以让你
If you really wanna watch that Serengeti thing,we can.
听着，你们绝对不会相信的…
Listen,you are not going to believe this...
…但是音乐电视上的歌声 不是我的
...but that is not me singing on the video.
你怎么知道的呢？
How did you find out?
唱片公司送了一张纸条来 叫我签名，要我同意…
The record company sent this paper for me to sign saying it's okay...
…他们找别人来替我唱的 那是我的第一个线索
...for someone else to sing for me. That was my first clue.
那你打算怎么办？
What will you do?
我没有办法跟这种人一起工作
I can't work with people who would do this.
那当然
Sure.
这个…这个可怜的女人
I mean,this poor woman.
什么女人？
What woman?
那个代唱的女人
The voice woman.
她的声音真是棒透了 可是她没有音乐电视啊
She has a great voice,but she doesn't have a video.
菲比，那你呢？
Okay,Pheebs,but what about you?
我有音乐电视，你得要用心听
I have a video. Pay attention.
这个代唱的人她很有才华
This voice woman,she's so talented.
可是那些制作人说 她长得不够好看之类的啦
But according to the producer people,she doesn't have the right look.
她就像那种 动物收容所里面的动物…
She's like one of those animals at the pound...
…没有人要就因为 她长得不够漂亮而已
...who nobody wants because they're not pretty.
或者是像只老狗，浑身发臭…
Or you know,like some old dog who's kind of like stinky and
我的天啊，她就是“臭臭猫”
Oh,my God! She's "smelly cat"!
那首歌好有深度
That song has so many levels.
艾迪
Hey,Eddie.
来玩桌上足球怎么样？
You wanna play some foosball?
不，谢了，老兄 我不太喜欢运动
No,thanks,man. I'm not really into sports.
好吧…
Yeah,okay. All right.
没关系 “海滩游侠”要开演了
Doesn't matter. Time for Baywatch!
你喜欢看那个节目？
You like that show?
你不喜欢吗？
You don't?
不，那只是一群俊男美女 在海滩上跑来跑去
It's just pretty people running around on the beach.
棒就棒在那里啊
That's the brilliance of it.
俊男美女
The pretty people.
跑来跑去
And the running.
我要进我房间看书了
I'm gonna go read in my room for a little while.
好的，老兄
Okay,man.
我想到和我相知相惜的友人
I think of all the friends I've known
但我拨电话时
But when I dial the telephone
没有人在家
No one's home
孤孤单单
All by myself
我不想要一个人
Don't wanna live
孤孤单单
All by myself
不想再孤单
Anymore
孤孤单单
All by myself
我的最后一首歌曲叫做“臭臭猫”
I'm gonna start off with a little song called "Smelly Cat. "
哦，为了消除你们的疑虑，我要说，这是我自己的声音
Oh, for those of you who are wondering, this is my real voice.
臭臭猫，臭臭猫
Smelly cat,smelly cat
他们喂你什么？ 一起唱
What are they feeding you? Everybody!
臭臭猫，臭臭猫
Smelly cat,smelly cat
那不是你的错
It's not your fault
他们不带你去看兽医
They won't take you to the vet
你显然不是他们的最爱
You're obviously not their favorite pet
你或许不是一床玫瑰
You may not be a bed of roses
也没有人会喜欢闻你
And you're no friend To those with noses
罗斯，歌词都唱完了，抱歉 好了，回到合唱的部分
Ross,those are the only lines we have. Back to the chorus!